

UX Researcher + Designer New York, NY janepark.me linkedin/in/janepark7 janeparkjp@gmail.com

I am a UX Researcher with design skills who identifies problems, strategies, and solutions to help deliver meaningful user experiences that create a social impact in our society. I am grounded in my previous hospitality and education experiences, where listening and learning from real people is always the first step to success.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Workshop In Business Opportunities (WIBO)** — *UX Designer + Researcher*

MARCH 2019 - MAY 2019

- Conducted end-to-end research studies, including recruiting interviews/usability testing, synthesis, and communicating findings and recommendations
- Managed a team by delegating weekly tasks, meeting deadlines, and organized weekly meetings
- Translated research insights into solutions by creating wireframes and medium-fidelity mockups

# **Upside Health** — Freelance UX Designer

**APRIL 2019** 

- Analyzed existing data and secondary research to inform design direction
- Collaborated with CEO and Head of Product to create a new feature for their product, Ouchie, for tracking pain management and history
- Designed and created the new interface for the feature, which is currently in development

# New York Code + Design Academy — Teaching Assistant

SEPTEMBER 2017 - MARCH 2019

- Mentored students through troubleshooting techniques to resolve issues in their projects
- Graded assignments and advised on best practices and implementation of user research methods

# Multiple NYC Bakeries & Restaurants — Pastry Cook to Pastry Sous Chef

SEPTEMBER 2011 - MAY 2016

## **EDUCATION**

**BeginEx** | UX Design Accelerated Program

New York Code + Design Academy | UX Design, Web Development Intensive
State University of New York at New Paltz | BA, Psychology
University of Huddersfield, UK | Study Abroad Psychology Program
Robert McKee's Storytelling Seminar | Three-day seminar on the craft of Storytelling

#### **SKILLS**

Data synthesization

Information

architecture

Interviews

Persona

Storytelling

Card sorting

Wireframing

Prototyping

\_ . .

Competitive analysis

Usability testing

User flows

### **TOOLS**

Sketch

Figma

Balsamiq

InVision

Marvel

Zeplin

Trello

## **DEVELOPMENT**

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

### **VOLUNTEER**

DesignOps Summit '18

### **HACKATHONS**

HexHacks 11/2018

BeginEx Design

Hackathon 3/2019